<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Open House &#8211; Hilton &amp; Hyland</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.hiltonhyland.com/properties/open-houses/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 22:26:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>440 Westbourne Drive</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/440-westbourne-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 02:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=93231</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Experience rare privacy and security on one of Weho&#8217;s most coveted streets. Park in your unique semi-circle driveway &#8211; ideal for hosting &#8211; before entering a poolside Mediterranean oasis. New teak decks wrap around this impeccably renovated home, leading to a fully-finished guesthouse, suitable for an office, recording studio, or income property. Ideal for entertainers [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience rare privacy and security on one of Weho&#8217;s most coveted streets. Park in your unique semi-circle driveway &#8211; ideal for hosting &#8211; before entering a poolside Mediterranean oasis. New teak decks wrap around this impeccably renovated home, leading to a fully-finished guesthouse, suitable for an office, recording studio, or income property. Ideal for entertainers or anyone seeking a relaxing, zen environment, this is indoor-outdoor living at its finest. The turn-key home features an open floor-plan, designer kitchen outfitted with Miele appliances, bar, and wine fridge and a primary suite with a wood-burning fireplace that opens directly to the smartly designed west-facing pool and spa. This chic and low-maintenance home is situated just minutes from the finest restaurants and shops in West Hollywood.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10743 Richland Ave</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/10743-richland-ave/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 02:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=93213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Best Value in Rancho Park: Custom Home offered at $925 per square foot! On an impressive, oversized lot, is one of the best opportunities in the zip. A Traditional dressed in charm and natural light, the entire space flaunts a bright ambiance through the glass roof dormers, French doors &#038; a picture window in the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Best Value in Rancho Park: Custom Home offered at $925 per square foot! On an impressive, oversized lot, is one of the best opportunities in the zip. A Traditional dressed in charm and natural light, the entire space flaunts a bright ambiance through the glass roof dormers, French doors &#038; a picture window in the main stairwell. Whitewashed interiors are remarkably contrasted with the solid dark oak flooring and richly accented family room, as vaulted ceilings spread the formal living and dining rooms. This movie-inspired chef&#8217;s kitchen has been upgraded with stainless steel appliances, a professional Thermadore Range, a Farmhouse sink, a water purification system, and Craftsman-style cabinetry. Inspired by Ralph Lauren, the sizeable primary bedroom suite boasts soaring vaulted ceilings, a custom period mantle &#038; rattan ceiling fan, and a cozy reading corner. The oversized spa bathroom is replete with a glass-enclosed steam room shower, a large jetted tub, separate vanity &#038; vestibule areas along with private water closet. Touting a wood-burning fireplace in the family room, a gas-burning fireplace in the primary, in-ceiling speakers throughout, and a 250+ bottle wine cellar, leisure has never been as accessible. A spacious grassy front and back yards enhance the home, while a separate area on the side of the residence is perfect for pets. An address destined for executives and discerning home buyers, this Westside Traditional in the Overland school district is easily the best offer in the neighborhood.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5028 Sunnyslope Ave</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/5028-sunnyslope-ave/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 02:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=93196</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Located in the center of one of the most desirable areas in Sherman Oaks stands this impeccably updated Contemporary Spanish home with a thoughtfully designed floor plan that can fit any family&#8217;s needs. Boasting 5 bedrooms and 4 bathrooms, this private home is fully gated with a brand-new wood-finished pedestrian gate and power driveway gate. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Located in the center of one of the most desirable areas in Sherman Oaks stands this impeccably updated Contemporary Spanish home with a thoughtfully designed floor plan that can fit any family&#8217;s needs. Boasting 5 bedrooms and 4 bathrooms, this private home is fully gated with a brand-new wood-finished pedestrian gate and power driveway gate. As soon as you enter, you are welcomed by a grand two-story entrance with elevated ceilings, wide plank white oak floors throughout, custom tile finished staircase, with the formal living room with custom wood finished floor to ceiling gas fireplace that flows into the large dining room with multi-layered ceiling finished with wood and illuminated by a restoration hardware light fixture. The open concept living and kitchen area with seamless flow to the backyard is perfect for cooking and watching the kids play outside, or to host any gathering. The oversized chef&#8217;s kitchen is fit with all top-of-the-line Thermador stainless steel appliances, tons of storage space and counter space, and features a quartz waterfall massive center island with plenty of seating. The large living space is highlighted by a custom-made wood finished gas fireplace with built-in floating shelves with easy access to the backyard. Downstairs is finished by an attached guest bedroom with separate exterior access, perfect for a playroom / guest suite / gym / or office. Upstairs you will find 4 bedrooms including the grand primary suite with large walk-in closet and a private balcony that overlooks the stunning backyard. The spa-like primary bathroom features dual vanities, large soaking tub, and glass enclosed shower with rainfall showerhead. 2 large guest bedrooms share a guest bath upstairs that has been tastefully updated. The large front guest bedroom is a junior ensuite featuring a large closet and window pouring in tons of natural light. The stunning private backyard has been completely designed around the art of entertaining or playing with the family, as it has been recently finished with turf and has lush greenery providing added security. Featuring a sparkling pebble tech pool and jacuzzi, covered outdoor dining space, strung up market lights, BBQ, and a large turf play area. Located next to multiple highly desirable schools, and just minutes away from the Westfield Fashion Mall, fantastic restaurants and stores, freeways, and Ventura Blvd. This home truly provides the perfect style and atmosphere for anyone to truly enjoy all the best that California has to offer. Do not miss out on this wonderful home!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10790 Wilshire Blvd #1704, Westwood CA 90024</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/10790-wilshire-blvd-1704-westwood-ca-90024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 22:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=93065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Newly completed, this view home of the highest accord, ascends to new heights with heart-stopping panoramas from nearly every corner into and beyond the Pacific horizon. Naturally lit by the southern California sunshine and warmed by a custom fireplace, there is no feeling quite like living in the sky. Of the plethora of improvements &#8211; [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Newly completed, this view home of the highest accord, ascends to new heights with heart-stopping panoramas from nearly every corner into and beyond the Pacific horizon. Naturally lit by the southern California sunshine and warmed by a custom fireplace, there is no feeling quite like living in the sky. Of the plethora of improvements &#8211; from the opening of the floorplan, the 48” luxury floor tiles imported directly from Spain, and the custom frameless raised height invisible hinged white oak doors – none stands out more than the new and secure lifestyle afforded to its residents. The kitchen displays incredible, fully custom maple wood cabinets and quartz countertops, while white oak and maple wood is featured throughout the abode. Brand-new hardware, appliances, and state-of-the-art technology spread the home with customizable LED’s expanding the entire suite.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9000 Cynthia St</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/9000-cynthia-st/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=92748</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Clean lines and rich interiors blend together to create an organic modern aesthetic in this fully remodeled residence in the heart of Los Angeles&#8217; premiere Norma Triangle. This condo has a welcoming spacious layout: from the open concept kitchen, breakfast nook &#038; formal dining areas, to the formal foyer &#038; living room. The 3rd floor [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Clean lines and rich interiors blend together to create an organic modern aesthetic in this fully remodeled residence in the heart of Los Angeles&#8217; premiere Norma Triangle. This condo has a welcoming spacious layout: from the open concept kitchen, breakfast nook &#038; formal dining areas, to the formal foyer &#038; living room. The 3rd floor vantage from its outdoor patio space and orientation facing south-west gives vistas from sunrise, West LA, &#038; awe-spired glittering lights of DTLA at sunset. Master bedroom with ensuite bath &#038; full dressing and custom walk-in closet areas create an escape within. A second bedroom &#038; bath give flexibility to home office or alternate guest suite. Laundry in the unit, Amenities on property include common pool, courtyards, community room and secured entrance. Included is tandem parking for two. Located one block to Beverly Hills and seconds from West Hollywood&#8217;s best shopping and dining!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3779 Colonial Ave</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/3779-colonial-ave/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 18:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=92727</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Conveniently located on the Westside, close to Venice, Santa Monica, and Mar Vista hotspots, sits this charming single-story home with numerous seller updates, including a detached bonus room. Enjoy the gated front yard, complete with a long driveway and drought friendly landscaping. Romantic and grassy backyard features string lights, fire pit, and flat concrete pad. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Conveniently located on the Westside, close to Venice, Santa Monica, and Mar Vista hotspots, sits this charming single-story home with numerous seller updates, including a detached bonus room. Enjoy the gated front yard, complete with a long driveway and drought friendly landscaping. Romantic and grassy backyard features string lights, fire pit, and flat concrete pad. The home enjoys classic, yet updated, features throughout including brick wood burning fireplace, new light fixtures/sconces, bay window with seating, durable hardwood floors, and extensive built-in storage. Bright and spacious kitchen is equipped with newer stainless-steel stove, range hood, dishwasher, and refrigerator. Primary bedroom suite has soaring ceilings, walk-in closet, and French doors with access to the backyard. Detached and finished bonus room enjoys tall ceilings, skylights, sliding glass doors, tankless-water heater, and contemporary bathroom. Leave as-is or convert into an ADU for extra income. Additional storage is available in a large shed behind the bonus room. Large outdoor mirror, green grill, and all items in storage shed are excluded from the sale.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>128 Georgina Ave #4</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/128-georgina-ave-4/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 18:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=92707</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[128 Georgina Ave #4 &#8211; A Santa Monica townhome steps away from Palisades Park with spectacular ocean views of the Queen&#8217;s Necklace, a private 3 car direct-access garage, and excellent school district. This unit features 2 bedrooms + 2.5 bathrooms, and a versatile loft space on the top floor with peekaboo ocean views ideal for [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>128 Georgina Ave #4 &#8211; A Santa Monica townhome steps away from Palisades Park with spectacular ocean views of the Queen&#8217;s Necklace, a private 3 car direct-access garage, and excellent school district. This unit features 2 bedrooms + 2.5 bathrooms, and a versatile loft space on the top floor with peekaboo ocean views ideal for an office, gym, artist studio, or extra bedroom. Upon entering, you are greeted with high ceilings, French doors leading to an outdoor patio, and plenty of natural light on this corner unit. The living room features a gas fireplace and opens up to a dining area which leads to the updated kitchen with stainless steel appliances and breakfast nook. The primary bedroom has 3 closets, vaulted wood-beam ceilings, patio access, and stairs leading up to the loft. The primary bathroom includes dual vanity, a separate shower, and jetted tub. This residence is part of a gated complex of 10 units with a subterranean garage and parking for up to 5 guest vehicles. Gain access to all four levels of the unit with a private elevator. Other amenities include: side-by-side laundry closet, plenty of street parking on Georgina Ave, and minutes away from the best dining and shopping off of Montana Ave, Ocean Ave, and The 3rd St Promenade.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2308 Grand Canal, Venice CA 90291</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/2308-grand-canal-venice-ca-90291/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=92351</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A 2010 architectural build on a rare west-facing lot with great indoor/outdoor flow and 360 degree views from the rooftop deck. This 4 bedroom + 4.5 bath Venice estate features floor to ceiling Fleetwood pocket sliders that give you access to an entertainer&#8217;s backyard. The chef&#8217;s outdoor kitchen includes a sink, ice maker, two refrigerators, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A 2010 architectural build on a rare west-facing lot with great indoor/outdoor flow and 360 degree views from the rooftop deck. This 4 bedroom + 4.5 bath Venice estate features floor to ceiling Fleetwood pocket sliders that give you access to an entertainer&#8217;s backyard. The chef&#8217;s outdoor kitchen includes a sink, ice maker, two refrigerators, two freezers, BBQ grill, and a commercial grade wok range. Enjoy sunsets in the stainless steel jetted hot tub, and sunbathe on the daybed with views to the Grand Canal. The first level includes a two-car garage, powder room, open concept living &#038; dining area + kitchen with a Sub-Zero fridge, two Sub-Zero freezer drawers, Miele dishwasher, a six-burner Wolf range + warming drawer, and coffee cabinet. As you move to the residence&#8217;s second level, you have two en-suite guest bedrooms on the east-end, a laundry room with a sink, and a luxurious primary suite fitted like a 5-star hotel. The primary bathroom features dual vanity with floating lights, wood-paneled walls, bathtub, and a spacious shower for two. Across the hall you are greeted with a walk-in closet through pocket doors. The primary bedroom is outfitted with custom fabric lined walls, vaulted ceilings, a gas fireplace, and three Juliette balconies overlooking the Venice Canals. The third level includes a twelve-person 3-level screening room with Restoration Hardware cloud sofas, a projector, and surround sound. On the opposite side you will find the fourth bedroom with a fireplace which was previously a game room + wet bar that has now been converted into an office. After a day of entertaining, enjoy a full body massage in the spa room equipped with a sauna, full bathroom, and French glass doors leading to a balcony. If you are not sold yet, wait until you see the oversized rooftop deck with unobstructed views of the Pacific ocean and the Santa Monica mountains. Other amenities include elevator access to all interior floors, recessed lighting, surround sound throughout, security cameras, and great walkability to restaurants such as Gran Blanco, Great White, and others off Abbot Kinney.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1011 Georgina Ave, Santa Monica CA 90402</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/1011-georgina-ave-santa-monica-ca-90402/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=92306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Brand new modern masterpiece located on one of the most coveted streets in Santa Monica. Beyond the gated entry and lush front yard, enter the home to experience the perfect blend of design and function. A combination of exposed board-formed concrete, French limestone and beautiful white oak cabinetry and floors deliver sophistication and understated elegance. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brand new modern masterpiece located on one of the most coveted streets in Santa Monica. Beyond the gated entry and lush front yard, enter the home to experience the perfect blend of design and function. A combination of exposed board-formed concrete, French limestone and beautiful white oak cabinetry and floors deliver sophistication and understated elegance. Anchoring this architectural marvel designed and built by Kevin McCauley is a custom, one-of-a-kind staircase that is truly a work of art. Crafted for indoor/outdoor entertaining, the Miele kitchen and family room&#8217;s sliding glass doors open to additional dining areas and a resort-like pool. The pool, with its cascading waterfalls and hot tub, is perfect for swimming laps or simply relaxing. Rounding out the main level is a formal living room, dining area, home office, bedroom, and powder room. An elevator accesses all levels of the home. The second level is comprised of three spacious ensuite bedrooms including the master, comfortable lounge/family room area, large laundry room and access to the rooftop deck. Unwind in the luxurious master suite with spa-like bathroom lined in beautiful marble, dual walk-in closets, wet-bar, and private master patio. A spacious lower level features a rec room, full bar, exercise area, theatre, bedroom, laundry and a number of storage rooms. The detached ADU is a fully outfitted one-bedroom guest house or office with living area, kitchen, bathroom, and separate entrance. This impeccable location is a short stroll to Montana Ave&#8217;s shops, restaurants, and glistening Pacific Ocean.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3060 Dona Susana Dr, Studio City CA 91604</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/3060-dona-susana-dr-studio-city-ca-91604/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=91723</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Magnificent Mid-Century Modern in the coveted Dona Hills of Studio City and situated on an expansive 11,700 SF lot with over 100 ft of frontage. Surrounded by lush landscaping filled with fresh citrus trees, roses and lavender &#8211; this single level home is the epitome of a true Southern California lifestyle. Upon entry, enjoy an [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Magnificent Mid-Century Modern in the coveted Dona Hills of Studio City and situated on an expansive 11,700 SF lot with over 100 ft of frontage. Surrounded by lush landscaping filled with fresh citrus trees, roses and lavender &#8211; this single level home is the epitome of a true Southern California lifestyle. Upon entry, enjoy an abundance of natural light showcased by vaulted ceilings, skylights and sliding glass doors, with a direct sightline to the quintessential yard and pool/spa outdoors. The updated interiors feature 3 spacious bedrooms, 3 luxuriously-appointed bathrooms, a formal dining room, family room, kitchen with breakfast nook and outdoor BBQ. Easily accessible to fine dining, shopping and nightlife of Studio City and the Sunset Strip, and located within a well-rated school district. Truly, an exceptional residence offering privacy, expansive entertaining areas both indoors and out, and timeless Los Angeles character.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
