<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sold &#8211; Hilton &amp; Hyland</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.hiltonhyland.com/properties/sold/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 18:17:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>North Bristol Ave &#124; Brentwood Park</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/north-bristol-drive-brentwood-park/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Delgado]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 22:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pristine, stately, and ideally positioned on a sprawling gated lot set high above the street. Discover this traditional masterpiece in exclusive Brentwood Park. With a very extensive custom renovation just completed, the estate showcases the perfect mix of cohesive design elements blending rustic textures and organic materials. The mix of classic traditional and contemporary design [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pristine, stately, and ideally positioned on a sprawling gated lot set high above the street.  Discover this traditional masterpiece in exclusive Brentwood Park.  With a very extensive custom renovation just completed, the estate showcases the perfect mix of cohesive design elements blending rustic textures and organic materials. The mix of classic traditional and contemporary design evokes feelings of warmth while understated elegance remains constant. The price stated is the asking price at the time of sale.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>224 Glenroy Pl Los Angeles CA 90049</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/224-glenroy-pl-los-angeles-ca-90049/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Delgado]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 19:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A fully privatized single-level home that exudes sophistication and style. Redone in a warm, yet simple design that is timeless. Set down from the street behind an impressive gate, a 3/4-acre lot has a Bel Air worthy approach. The open layout is anchored by light oak flooring throughout. The canyon facing rooms reveal the rear [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fully privatized single-level home that exudes sophistication and style. Redone in a warm, yet simple design that is timeless. Set down from the street behind an impressive gate, a 3/4-acre lot has a Bel Air worthy approach. The open layout is anchored by light oak flooring throughout. The canyon facing rooms reveal the rear yard with sliding glass doors to enjoy an indoor/outdoor lifestyle. Kitchen provides Miele, Wolf and Sub-Zero appliances with Caesar stone counter tops. Artistry lighting by Plug and fixtures by RH. Beyond the expansive flat and grassed main yard is a lower pad. Add a pool here, or utilize the land for redevelopment. With feasibility study indicating you can build appx. 17,000 sq ft, there is amazing potential for new construction to boast sweeping jetliner views of the city to the ocean, and Catalina. Three car garage, maids room off kitchen and a bonus den offers you options. Come experience this serene and verdant setting, and discover what is a truly remarkable opportunity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>565 Tigertail Road, Brentwood</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/565-tigertail-road-brentwood/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Delgado]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 19:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>710 4th Ave #4</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/710-4th-ave-4/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=88758</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Situated seconds off Abbot Kinney and Rose Ave &#8211; this bright and exquisite townhome is your perfect opportunity to live, work and create from the comfort of your own home! Flooded with natural light, and spacious/open floor plan, this property feels more like a single-family residence, with a design that offers you functional and flexible [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Situated seconds off Abbot Kinney and Rose Ave &#8211; this bright and exquisite townhome is your perfect opportunity to live, work and create from the comfort of your own home! Flooded with natural light, and spacious/open floor plan, this property feels more like a single-family residence, with a design that offers you functional and flexible options on how to utilize the space.// You&#8217;ll Love The welcoming main living area that offers soaring ceilings, a floor to ceiling fireplace that is a centerpiece to the space. Don&#8217;t miss the perfectly sized balcony and downstairs private landscaped patio that will fill the space with ocean breezes. Beautiful built-ins envelop the room for ample storage. Upstairs enjoy your, private cozy, master bedroom loft.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Confidential Beverly Hills View Property</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/beverly-hills-view-property/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 23:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=88718</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>11107 Braddock Dr, Culver City CA</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/11107-braddock-dr-culver-city-ca/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=88283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fantastic opportunity to live in the Veteran&#8217;s Park neighborhood, just a 2-minute skip from Culver City&#8217;s sought after Farragut Elementary, Culver Middle &#038; High School. Charming home with artistic entry and desirable open floor-plan: Larger galley kitchen with peninsula opens onto dining area and living room all making up a &#8220;great room&#8221; ideal for entertaining [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fantastic opportunity to live in the Veteran&#8217;s Park neighborhood, just a 2-minute skip from Culver City&#8217;s sought after Farragut Elementary, Culver Middle &#038; High School. Charming home with artistic entry and desirable open floor-plan: Larger galley kitchen with peninsula opens onto dining area and living room all making up a &#8220;great room&#8221; ideal for entertaining enjoyment. Living room has pitched beamed ceilings, stately stone fireplace and double glass doors leading into a sunroom and backyard with patio area and pool. Three spacious bedrooms, plus enclosed patio &#8220;sun room&#8221; and detached &#8220;bonus room&#8221; adjacent to pool, makes for a perfect office/ play room. Central Heating, newer windows, newer hardwood floors and fresh paint make this a home ready to move in and enjoy! Great location, close to Veteran&#8217;s Park, schools, restaurants, shops, downtown Culver City, Playa Vista and all that the greater Westside has to offer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10517 Mars Ln, Bel Air CA 90077</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/10517-mars-ln-bel-air-ca-90077/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 22:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=87811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nestled above the treetops, with captivating views and the privacy of lush landscaping, is a tastefully designed residence offering indoor/outdoor California living. Enter to bright light in an open floor plan with picture windows capturing the views of trees and mountain tops. Clean, sleek feel with porcelain floors, and designer finishes throughout the house, including [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nestled above the treetops, with captivating views and the privacy of lush landscaping, is a tastefully designed residence offering indoor/outdoor California living. Enter to bright light in an open floor plan with picture windows capturing the views of trees and mountain tops. Clean, sleek feel with porcelain floors, and designer finishes throughout the house, including the guest bath. Custom kitchen with a Wolf subzero package, Caesarstone counters, and pull-out shelves. Separate laundry room off the kitchen.Walk outside to an IPE wood sundeck for your morning coffee, afternoon BBQ, or just watch the hummingbirds.Three wonderful ensuite bedrooms, with an oversized shower and dual vanity in the primary bedroom, and generous built-in closets.At the end of a private driveway is a two-car garage, with storage and workstation.Conveniently located near Bev Hills and Century City.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1630 S Crest Dr, Beverlywood CA 90035</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/1630-s-crest-dr-beverlywood-ca-90035/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 22:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=87805</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Charming English country home in coveted Pico &#8211; Robertson neighborhood, one of the best places to live in California. Spacious, bright, and well maintained, with fabulous features throughout such as gorgeous vaulted ceilings, elegant formal dining room with a cozy wood and gas burning fireplace, double pane windows with shutters throughout, new drywall, new paint, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Charming English country home in coveted Pico &#8211; Robertson neighborhood, one of the best places to live in California. Spacious, bright, and well maintained, with fabulous features throughout such as gorgeous vaulted ceilings, elegant formal dining room with a cozy wood and gas burning fireplace, double pane windows with shutters throughout, new drywall, new paint, hardwood flooring throughout, brand new plumbing, spa tubs in both remodeled bathrooms. A large permitted rec-room converted garage with bathroom and kitchenette. Close to shopping, dining, Canfield Elementary, entertainment, short distance to Beverly Hills, Downtown, Culver City. Enjoy the best Beverlywood Community has to offer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>17190 Avenida De Santa Ynez, Pacific Palisades Ca 90272</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/17190-avenida-de-santa-ynez-pacific-palisades-ca-90272/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 21:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=87770</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fabulous 4 bedroom, 3 bath residence of approximately 3,387 square feet located on a large corner lot in a convenient spot within the Palisades Highlands. The home enjoys wonderful canyon and mountain views, and the spacious yard with private pool, spa, barbeque and fire pit is ideal for entertaining. The lower level features gated access, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fabulous 4 bedroom, 3 bath residence of approximately 3,387 square feet located on a large corner lot in a convenient spot within the Palisades Highlands. The home enjoys wonderful canyon and mountain views, and the spacious yard with private pool, spa, barbeque and fire pit is ideal for entertaining. The lower level features gated access, a dramatic entry and living room with stone fireplace and walls of glass, a formal dining room, a bright center- island kitchen and breakfast area, a family room, and a bedroom and bath that work beautifully as a private office suite. Additional features include a wine cellar, storage area, laundry room and a direct access 2-car garage. The upper level includes a gracious master suite with stunning mountain views, two additional bedrooms and a spacious bath. Membership privileges include access to a recreation center with gym, tennis courts, play area and community pool and spa.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1333 14Th St #6, Santa Monica CA.</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/1333-14th-st-6-santa-monica-ca/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Richard Carrillo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 18:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=86976</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to 1333 14th St, unit no. 6, an idyllic 2-bedroom residence situated in a prime and convenient Santa Monica location. Down a gated &#038; secure tree-lined walkway, you enter this lovely home which has been meticulously cared for and is in impeccable condition. Some of the beautiful finishes include bamboo floors, oak cabinetry, recessed [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to 1333 14th St, unit no. 6, an idyllic 2-bedroom residence situated in a prime and convenient Santa Monica location. Down a gated &#038; secure tree-lined walkway, you enter this lovely home which has been meticulously cared for and is in impeccable condition. Some of the beautiful finishes include bamboo floors, oak cabinetry, recessed lighting, and plantation shutters. An open, light-filled floor plan connects the spacious living, dining, and kitchen areas. Down the main hall you find two comfortable bedrooms and two bathrooms. Enjoy cool coastal breezes and a glass of wine on the covered outdoor patio. Ideally positioned at the rear of the building, the home is well-above ground level, and is quiet and peaceful. Exterior cosmetic upgrades have been completed, so unlike many other condominium buildings in Santa Monica, 1333 14th boasts outstanding curb appeal and common areas. The ultimate in California living; a short distance to restaurants and shopping, and just 14 blocks from world-class beaches and the glistening Pacific Ocean.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
