<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sale &#8211; Hilton &amp; Hyland</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.hiltonhyland.com/properties/sale/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:23:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>23618 Malibu Colony Rd #56</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/23618-malibu-colony-rd-56/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96908</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Located in the exclusive guard-gated community of Malibu Colony sits this exquisitely designed home featured and on the cover of Architectural Digest. The open floor plan is luxuriously furnished including a gourmet kitchen that flows into the living room with a fireplace and vaulted wood paneled ceilings throughout. A sun filled loft area above the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Located in the exclusive guard-gated community of Malibu Colony sits this exquisitely designed home featured and on the cover of Architectural Digest. The open floor plan is luxuriously furnished including a gourmet kitchen that flows into the living room with a fireplace and vaulted wood paneled ceilings throughout. A sun filled loft area above the living room is complete with a bed and wide open views of Colony beach. The elegant primary suite includes a canopy bed, sitting area, walk-in closet, and a beautifully appointed bathroom. Additionally, there is a separate attached private guest bedroom with an ensuite bathroom. The outdoor patio is perfect for dining and showcases multiple dining areas, lounge chairs, spa, outdoor shower, bbq, and an outdoor fireplace. Close distance to the best boutique shops and restaurants Malibu has to offer. 3 month minimum.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>603 Boccaccio Ave</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/603-boccaccio-ave/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 21:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96893</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Located in the very heart of Venice, near the beach and only a few blocks from Abbot Kinney&#8217;s long stretch of always trendy shopping, restaurants and bars, this modern duplex is certain to appeal to a wide range of buyers and investors. The fully fenced-in and highly private lot is comprised of two superb units. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Located in the very heart of Venice, near the beach and only a few blocks from Abbot Kinney&#8217;s long stretch of always trendy shopping, restaurants and bars, this modern duplex is certain to appeal to a wide range of buyers and investors. The fully fenced-in and highly private lot is comprised of two superb units. The front units is a 3 bedroom/2 bathroom house featuring an open concept kitchen/living room with vaulted ceilings, fireplace, breakfast bar, custom built-in shelving and custom shutters. Additional features include fully paid solar panels, central air w/NEST thermostat, a gated and hedged front yard, two courtyard patios, lushly packed garden beds and a 2-car garage with direct in-home access. The second unit, which sits directly above the garage, is a spacious and charming light and bright 1 bedroom/1 bathroom that has its own gated and private terrace. The open concept floor plan features a living room with fireplace, dining area, kitchen with breakfast bar, vaulted ceilings, air conditioning, an amply sized bedroom with large walk-in closet and a bright bathroom with shower and bathtub. Additional amenities for this second unit include its own dedicated parking spot next to the unit and laundry area access . Both units afford a great deal of exceptional inter-unit privacy. Front house was photographed prior to current tenant occupancy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3404 Colville Pl</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/3404-colville-pl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[3404 Colville Pl &#8211; A single story mid-century fixer located at the end of a cul-de-sac on a 14,000 sq ft lot with breathtaking 180 degree views of the San Gabriel Mountains and within the Lanai School District boundaries. This is the first time this property has been on the market since it was built [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>3404 Colville Pl &#8211; A single story mid-century fixer located at the end of a cul-de-sac on a 14,000 sq ft lot with breathtaking 180 degree views of the San Gabriel Mountains and within the Lanai School District boundaries. This is the first time this property has been on the market since it was built &#8211; a rare opportunity to make this your next dream home or maximize value by adding an additional 1,253 sq ft per UnderBuilt Report. As you enter the house, you are immediately greeted with sweeping views from all angles of the great room, which include the living and dining areas as well as a sunken bar, giving you that classic mid-century vibe. This functional floor plan has the primary bedroom and two bedrooms on one side, and a den and guest quarters on the other side. The primary bedroom and bathroom offer excellent views with direct access to a private side yard. On the opposite end is a kitchen which can possibly be expanded into the enclosed outdoor patio. Enjoy sunbathing or add an infinity pool to the backyard with some of the best views Encino has to offer. Just off of Mulholland and within close proximity to Brentwood and Beverly Hills.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>24 Eastwind St #1</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/24-eastwind-st-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96864</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[24 Eastwind St #1 &#8211; A stunning architectural townhouse with gorgeous ocean views in the Marina Peninsula sitting on a private walk-street less than 85 yards from one of the most secluded beaches on the Westside and within an excellent primary school district, Coeur D&#8217;Alene. As you step into the gate-accessed courtyard of this 2-unit [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>24 Eastwind St #1 &#8211; A stunning architectural townhouse with gorgeous ocean views in the Marina Peninsula sitting on a private walk-street less than 85 yards from one of the most secluded beaches on the Westside and within an excellent primary school district, Coeur D&#8217;Alene. As you step into the gate-accessed courtyard of this 2-unit building, you are greeted with a koi fountain display &#038; serene garden with a private outdoor shower to take off the sand before heading inside this 3 bedroom + loft &#038; 3.5 bath townhome. The first level of the unit offers a separate guest bedroom and bathroom, as well as access to the 4-car shared garage (2 car tandem + 1 car in front of garage). The second guest bedroom and primary bedrooms are located on the second floor, each with their own en-suite bathrooms and ocean views. The primary bedroom includes a fireplace, private balcony, and the en-suite bathroom features dual vanity, a jetted tub, and separate shower. The third level features over 30 windows showcasing ocean and mountain views in every corner of the living, kitchen, and dining areas. Massive 40 ft ceilings in the stairwell offer plenty of sun through the two large skylights, with an abundance of dramatic wall space to display all your artwork. The open loft space above the third floor is ideal for an office or studio with a powder room for your guests, and direct access to a spacious rooftop deck with room to entertain up to 15. Other amenities include a gourmet chef&#8217;s kitchen with stainless steel appliances, Sub-Zero refrigerator, Italian cabinetry, and a few blocks away from shopping and dining. Make sure to watch the detailed walkthrough video on YouTube!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>321 N Oakhurst Dr #404</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/321-n-oakhurst-dr-404/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In Beverly Hills is a Contemporary space carefully curated for 90210 lifestyles. North of Burton between L&#8217;Ermitage and Four Seasons is your own personal resort. Above the treetops is a fourth-floor home of the highest accord. The public rooms are spread with soft ceramic-tiled floors while natural wood floors grace the bedrooms. Freshly installed quartz [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Beverly Hills is a Contemporary space carefully curated for 90210 lifestyles. North of Burton between L&#8217;Ermitage and Four Seasons is your own personal resort. Above the treetops is a fourth-floor home of the highest accord. The public rooms are spread with soft ceramic-tiled floors while natural wood floors grace the bedrooms. Freshly installed quartz countertops, the new backsplash, and state-of-the-art appliances dress your culinary studio while chandeliers, a custom fireplace and an ivory finish creates an elegant ambiance. Overlooking the city from your private perch, the primary double-vanity en-suite has a personal balcony with ample lounging space and a view. Neighbors to luxury retail and fine dining with 24/7 private front desk security, 321 No. Oakhurst Dr. is a one-of-a-kind opportunity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>788 Tortuoso Way</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/788-tortuoso-way/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 22:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=95018</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A modern concept by Architect William Hefner, 788 Tortuoso Way is a majestic 3 acre site in the heart of Old Bel Air. A proposed compound of 17,000 or 23,000 sqft for generations to come. Major views from Ocean to Westwood. Long private driveway. Room for tennis court, guest house and acres of grass. Surrounded [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> A modern concept by Architect William Hefner, 788 Tortuoso Way is a majestic 3 acre site in the heart of Old Bel Air. A proposed compound of 17,000 or 23,000 sqft for generations to come. Major views from Ocean to Westwood. Long private driveway. Room for tennis court, guest house and acres of grass. Surrounded by estates in excess of $150M. Directly across from famed Hotel Bel Air. Beyond special in every way.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1449 Summitridge</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/1449-summitridge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 02:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=94655</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While most homes are derived from design, 1449 Summitridge is bonafide artwork. Behind a unique Art Deco facade and on a double lot is just under 2000 sqft of curated space. The home consists of 2 spacious bedrooms and 2 bathrooms with a non-permitted third full bath on the lower level by outdoor gym/spa (Buyer [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While most homes are derived from design, 1449 Summitridge is bonafide artwork. Behind a unique Art Deco facade and on a double lot is just under 2000 sqft of curated space. The home consists of 2 spacious bedrooms and 2 bathrooms with a non-permitted third full bath on the lower level by outdoor gym/spa (Buyer to verify all information). With a rare opportunity to turn an additional 1200 SqFt of Beverly Hills soil into whatever your dreams desire, this added space has already been approved for building. Whether a glistening pool, impressive guest house, or entertainment room, the second lot is ready for your next venture. Situated next to a protected hillside, the privacy offered by only having one neighbor is priceless. The quality of the home is unmistakable with nearly half a million improvements over the past two years. The elevated ambiance is perfectly paired with spectacular views and encompassing panoramas. Whether on the lower terrace with the 10-person hot tub, separate shower space, outdoor gym, and lounge area or on the main level terrace, you constantly capture picturesque cityscapes and iridescent sunsets. Dressed in hand-selected amenities, the entire abode has been upgraded. The luxury is beyond evident: from the state-of-the-art kitchen space with a mobile center island to the infrared sauna, cold plunge, and dedicated home office, welcome to paradise. The primary en-suite features its own personal door to a secluded balcony and a stunning display of natural light, while the bathroom may be the most impressive portion of the home. Built to create one of the most opulent bathrooms in the city, the imported marble and quartz tiling pales in comparison to the separate shower room and free-standing black marble tub that showcases the incredible skyline and views over the treetops. A haven for entertaining and a North of Sunset escape from the city only minutes from the Flats, 1449 Summitridge Drive is a one-of-a-kind opportunity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2054 Roscomore</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/2054-roscomore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=94420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elegant traditional home in a serene Bel Air setting. Featuring an open floor plan with high ceilings, hardwood floors, and natural light beaming through numerous glass walls. Expansive living and family room, office, gym, and modern kitchen with stainless steel appliances and stone center island. The second floor boasts luxurious bedrooms with spacious closets and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elegant traditional home in a serene Bel Air setting. Featuring an open floor plan with high ceilings, hardwood floors, and natural light beaming through numerous glass walls. Expansive living and family room, office, gym, and modern kitchen with stainless steel appliances and stone center island. The second floor boasts luxurious bedrooms with spacious closets and ensuite baths. Relax in the lavish master suite featuring vaulted ceilings, a cozy fireplace, a soaker tub, walk-in closets, and a balcony overlooking verdant grounds. Ideal for entertaining, this property includes a swimmer&#8217;s pool, spa, patio, and BBQ. The guesthouse features a deluxe sauna and steam room with shower. Lush landscaped yard leads to terraced gardens and abundance of fruit trees.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1120 Wallace Ridge</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/1120-wallace-ridge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=94147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Award-winning Prime Trousdale designed by master architect Edward Fickett, FAIA. This tennis court estate, with grandfathered in night lights that can never be done again in Trousdale, features privacy, volume, and resort-like amenities. Tucked behind gates, this impressive residence is situated on a jumbo lot, boasts architectural pedigree, floor-to-ceiling windows, and A+ views of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Award-winning Prime Trousdale designed by master architect Edward Fickett, FAIA. This tennis court estate, with grandfathered in night lights that can never be done again in Trousdale, features privacy, volume, and resort-like amenities. Tucked behind gates, this impressive residence is situated on a jumbo lot, boasts architectural pedigree, floor-to-ceiling windows, and A+ views of the city and Pacific Ocean. Home is move-in ready, but the historical tag has been removed which allows for major renovations to be done if desired. A buyer can choose to move forward with the approved plans to expand on the historical nature of the property, which already include 18&#8242; ceilings and dramatic roof elevation change, or keep it in its current state. Double door entry reveals an open and versatile floor plan showcasing a light-and-bright formal living room, an indoor living tree and an elevated dining room. A spacious upstairs primary suite has it all; a loft area, dual bathrooms, walk-in closets, and a terrace with breathtaking views. The sun drenched, dine-in, gourmet kitchen was renovated with a bold, yet classic palette and finished with a large island counter, breakfast bar, and fine appliances. A sitting room features an entertainer&#8217;s bar, a double-sided fireplace, treetop views and access to a flat grassy outdoor pad. The home&#8217;s exterior offers an inviting backyard with pool and large patio, a full-size and flood-lit n/s tennis court, fire pit, and a generous space for a gathering. Close to all that Beverly Hills has to offer, this offering is not to be missed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>440 Westbourne Drive</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/440-westbourne-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 02:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=93231</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Experience rare privacy and security on one of Weho&#8217;s most coveted streets. Park in your unique semi-circle driveway &#8211; ideal for hosting &#8211; before entering a poolside Mediterranean oasis. New teak decks wrap around this impeccably renovated home, leading to a fully-finished guesthouse, suitable for an office, recording studio, or income property. Ideal for entertainers [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience rare privacy and security on one of Weho&#8217;s most coveted streets. Park in your unique semi-circle driveway &#8211; ideal for hosting &#8211; before entering a poolside Mediterranean oasis. New teak decks wrap around this impeccably renovated home, leading to a fully-finished guesthouse, suitable for an office, recording studio, or income property. Ideal for entertainers or anyone seeking a relaxing, zen environment, this is indoor-outdoor living at its finest. The turn-key home features an open floor-plan, designer kitchen outfitted with Miele appliances, bar, and wine fridge and a primary suite with a wood-burning fireplace that opens directly to the smartly designed west-facing pool and spa. This chic and low-maintenance home is situated just minutes from the finest restaurants and shops in West Hollywood.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
