<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Leases &#8211; Hilton &amp; Hyland</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.hiltonhyland.com/properties/leases/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>23618 Malibu Colony Rd #56</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/23618-malibu-colony-rd-56/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=96908</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Located in the exclusive guard-gated community of Malibu Colony sits this exquisitely designed home featured and on the cover of Architectural Digest. The open floor plan is luxuriously furnished including a gourmet kitchen that flows into the living room with a fireplace and vaulted wood paneled ceilings throughout. A sun filled loft area above the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Located in the exclusive guard-gated community of Malibu Colony sits this exquisitely designed home featured and on the cover of Architectural Digest. The open floor plan is luxuriously furnished including a gourmet kitchen that flows into the living room with a fireplace and vaulted wood paneled ceilings throughout. A sun filled loft area above the living room is complete with a bed and wide open views of Colony beach. The elegant primary suite includes a canopy bed, sitting area, walk-in closet, and a beautifully appointed bathroom. Additionally, there is a separate attached private guest bedroom with an ensuite bathroom. The outdoor patio is perfect for dining and showcases multiple dining areas, lounge chairs, spa, outdoor shower, bbq, and an outdoor fireplace. Close distance to the best boutique shops and restaurants Malibu has to offer. 3 month minimum.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1220 Corsica</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/1220-corsica/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Axanti Anthony]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 22:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=95025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to 1220 Corsica Dr, a beautiful &#038; welcoming single-story home in the super prime lower Riviera. The home is in great condition, has a wonderful layout with four bedrooms and an office, and is sited on a lush, private lot with oasis like grounds including a pool and hot tub. The perfect short-term furnished [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to 1220 Corsica Dr, a beautiful &#038; welcoming single-story home in the super prime lower Riviera. The home is in great condition, has a wonderful layout with four bedrooms and an office, and is sited on a lush, private lot with oasis like grounds including a pool and hot tub. The perfect short-term furnished rental, available now for an approximate 4 to 6 month rental. Professional photography is coming soon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>313 S Oakhurst Dr, Beverly Hills CA 90212</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/313-s-oakhurst-dr-beverly-hills-ca-90212/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=92200</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Custom built Mediterranean on quiet tree lined street. Perfect family home with 5 bedrooms, 5-1/2 baths all ensuite. High ceilings and wood floors throughout. Expansive formal living room with fireplace, open gourmet chef&#8217;s kitchen with top-of-the line appliances, granite counter tops, custom wood cabinetry and separate island, connects to large family room with fireplace. Butler&#8217;s [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Custom built Mediterranean on quiet tree lined street. Perfect family home with 5 bedrooms, 5-1/2 baths all ensuite. High ceilings and wood floors throughout. Expansive formal living room with fireplace, open gourmet chef&#8217;s kitchen with top-of-the line appliances, granite counter tops, custom wood cabinetry and separate island, connects to large family room with fireplace. Butler&#8217;s pantry leads to formal dining room with doors opening out to front courtyard for additional al fresco dining. Beautiful green backyard and patio with privacy for outdoor entertaining. Includes entertainment system with several TVs, built in speakers, TV in master bath, surround sound system, security camera system throughout the house and alarm system. Gated and secured driveway for at least 5 cars, and 2 additional side-by-side parking spaces in front of the gate. Walking distance to Beverly Hills top schools, Synagogue, shops, restaurants, groceries, gas, dry cleaners, gym and more. Ready for immediate move in. Garage not included with lease.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>647 N Poinsettia Pl, Los Angeles, CA 90036</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/647-n-poinsettia-pl-los-angeles-ca-90036/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=90724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[$2.25 psf per month NNN Approximately 1,287 sqft]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>$2.25 psf per month NNN<br />
Approximately 1,287 sqft</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1247 Roberto Ln, Los Angeles, CA 90077</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/1247-roberto-ln-los-angeles-ca-90077-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AgentImage]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 23:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=90032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nestled in the heart of Bel-Air &#038; among the city&#8217;s most celebrated estates, sits this gated Mediterranean view home w/ incredible scale &#038; amenities. All living areas feature sweeping views of city lights, ocean &#038; mountains. Bright &#038; stunning entry w/ high ceilings &#038; skylights. Inviting kitchen is complete w/ granite island &#038; high-end appliances. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nestled in the heart of Bel-Air &#038; among the city&#8217;s most celebrated estates, sits this gated Mediterranean view home w/ incredible scale &#038; amenities.</p>
<p>All living areas feature sweeping views of city lights, ocean &#038; mountains. Bright &#038; stunning entry w/ high ceilings &#038; skylights. Inviting kitchen is complete w/ granite island &#038; high-end appliances. Breakfast bar opens to expansive living room, feat. floor-to-ceiling windows, Canadian Maple wood floors &#038; charming fireplace. Warm &#038; sunny formal living room enjoys double sliding doors that lead to a covered heated travertine patio &#038; generous backyard. Dining Room enjoys adj. al-fresco option, complete w/ infrared heaters &#038; stunning views. Other indoor amenities: library, office &#038; media room. Master BR enjoys walls of glass, fireplace, large private terrace, gym, walk-in closet &#038; massive views. Estate is complete w/ a private backyard featuring grassy area, infinity edge pool, spa, fire pit &#038; covered BBQ &#038; dining area.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>820 N. Fairfax Ave, Los Angeles CA 90046</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/820-n-fairfax-ave-los-angeles-ca-90046/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 19:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=86996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ONE OF A KIND PROPERTY! TOTAL GEM! Multitude of uses offices, retail and/or showroom space. This free standing building is centrally located on Fairfax Avenue between Melrose Avenue and Santa Monica Blvd adjacent to Blue Bottle Coffee, AESOP, and numerous entertainment companies. The building features a mostly wide open space, kitchen, vaulted ceilings, two walled [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ONE OF A KIND PROPERTY! TOTAL GEM! Multitude of uses offices, retail and/or showroom space. This free standing building is centrally located on Fairfax Avenue between Melrose Avenue and Santa Monica Blvd adjacent to Blue Bottle Coffee, AESOP, and numerous entertainment companies. The building features a mostly wide open space, kitchen, vaulted ceilings, two walled in private patio areas, natural light, and excellent parking in the front.</p>
<p>$8,250 SF/MO NNN<br />
Approximately 1,470 sf<br />
Showroom/Office/Retail</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>258 S. Beverly Dr Beverly Hills, CA 90212</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/86990/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 18:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=86990</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[$7.00 psf per month MG Approximately 2,281 sqft Restaurant/Cafe]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>$7.00 psf per month MG<br />
Approximately 2,281 sqft<br />
Restaurant/Cafe</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3311 Clerendon Rd, Beverly Hills CA. 90210</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/3311-clerendon-rd-beverly-hills-ca-90210/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Richard Carrillo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 17:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=85907</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tucked away in one of LA&#8217;s most sought after gated communities, this 7 bed, 9 bath Mulholland Estates grand Mediterranean is situated on 2/3&#8217;s of an acre. Enter to soaring ceiling heights throughout with a grand 2 story entry, formal living room and oversized formal dining room, large open concept kitchen/family room, beautiful den/media room, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tucked away in one of LA&#8217;s most sought after gated communities, this 7 bed, 9 bath Mulholland Estates grand Mediterranean is situated on 2/3&#8217;s of an acre. Enter to soaring ceiling heights throughout with a grand 2 story entry, formal living room and oversized formal dining room, large open concept kitchen/family room, beautiful den/media room, palatial master suite with sitting area entertainers backyard with beautiful pool, spa, casita /open cabana with a kitchen, barbeque, separate outdoor bath &#038; a one of a kind flat backyard the size of a soccer field.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>23457 Malibu Colony Rd #87A Malibu CA 90265</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/23457-malibu-colony-rd-87a-malibu-ca-90265/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 19:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=84662</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Located in the exclusive guard-gated community of Malibu Colony, This newly updated traditional beach residence is set on a rare double lot with approximately 107.5 feet of width. The private backyard oasis includes a lagoon style pool &#038; spa with a rock waterfall &#038; slide, renovated north-south private tennis court, full outdoor built-in BBQ area, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Located in the exclusive guard-gated community of Malibu Colony, This newly updated traditional beach residence is set on a rare double lot with approximately 107.5 feet of width. The private backyard oasis includes a lagoon style pool &#038; spa with a rock waterfall &#038; slide, renovated north-south private tennis court, full outdoor built-in BBQ area, a fire pit, and a separate detached guest house. Upper level primary bedroom suite features a spa like bathroom, walk-in closet, as well as large double doors that lead you to the wrap around terrace. Breathtaking views of the Santa Monica mountains, golf course, Malibu lagoon, and ocean. Completely furnished, lots of street parking, and direct beach access across the street through lot #87. This is the ultimate rental, for the perfect Malibu getaway, in the most desirable setting.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>8446 Kirkwood Dr, Sunset Strip CA 90046</title>
		<link>https://www.hiltonhyland.com/property/8446-kirkwood-dr-sunset-strip-ca-90046/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed Leyson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.hiltonhyland.com/?post_type=aios-listings&#038;p=83953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On a quiet tree-lined street in the Hollywood Hills, this newly rebuilt, exquisite Laurel Canyon original showcases warm, contemporary architecture that beautifully melds sophistication and simplicity. Gated and hedged for privacy, the five-bedroom residence features extraordinary attention to detail, masterful craftsmanship and seamless indoor-outdoor living for enjoying the quintessential California lifestyle. Enter the light, bright [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On a quiet tree-lined street in the Hollywood Hills, this newly rebuilt, exquisite Laurel Canyon original showcases warm, contemporary architecture that beautifully melds sophistication and simplicity. Gated and hedged for privacy, the five-bedroom residence features extraordinary attention to detail, masterful craftsmanship and seamless indoor-outdoor living for enjoying the quintessential California lifestyle. Enter the light, bright interiors where double-height windows soar over the foyer and floating wood staircase. To the right, an inviting, sunlit living room is ideal for welcoming guests. Upstairs, the open, airy great room boasts living and dining areas, a fireplace and expansive window walls framing leafy hillside views. The gourmet chefs kitchen features a spacious waterfall island, breakfast bar, premier stainless steel appliances and a vibrant blend of light, dark, wood and stone accents.</p>
<p> Folding glass doors open to reveal the private backyard oasis, ideal for gathering and entertaining. The resort-style pool with spouting water features is surrounded by sun-drenched terraces and a fireplace for unwinding under the stars. The outdoor living spaces also feature an alfresco dining terrace with a BBQ kitchen and a separate fire pit lounge. Five bedrooms include a stunning primary suite with two walk-in closets and magnificent spa-style bath with a freestanding soaking tub, separate vanities and direct access to the pool terrace. One bedroom currently serves as an office, while each of the 4.5 baths showcases distinct design and exquisite detail. Additional home features include one covered parking spot and gated parking for four additional vehicles, an enterprise grade, state of the art network system. From its tranquil, private hillside setting, the home is located within minutes of Laurel Canyon Blvd and the renowned shopping, dining and entertainment of the Sunset Strip.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
